Md. Khasrur Rahman

Full Stack Developer

Website: portfolio-ratin.com

GitHub: github.com/KhasrurRahman

LinkedIn: in/khasrur-rahmna



Mobile: +8801761955765

Email: Khasrur8@gmail.com

Address: Mohammadpur, Dhaka

About Me



I have 3.5 years of experience specializing in front end back end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic projects. Having an in-depth knowledge including advanced HTML5, CSS, CSS3, PHP, LARAVEL, JAVASCRIPT, VUEJS, AJAX, jQuery, C, MySql, Advance sql query. Strong background in management and leadership.

SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3 PHP LARAVEL JAVASCRIPT WORDPRESS **MYSQL VUE JS**

AJAX JAVA **MYSQL**

ADVANCE SQL QUERY VIDEO EDTING

SOFTWARE

PHP STORM WEB STROM **NETBINS PYCHARM** SUBLINE TEXT NAVICAT WINSCP **JUPYTER**

SONY VAGAS PRO MICROSOFT WORD

PUTTY

PERSONAL

COMMUNICATION PROBLEM SOLVING **DEDICATION TEAMWORK CREATIVITY**

EXPERIENCE



SOFTWARE ENGINEER, TRUST INNOVATION LIMITED (Bangladesh Army)

Dhaka, Bangladesh — OCT 2020-Present

Trust Innovation Limited (TIL), a sister concern of Bangladesh Army Welfare Trust, is a professional ICT solution provider and a valuable partner of Bangladesh Army.

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER, BD24REPORT

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Nov 2019-Oct 2020

bd24report.com is one of the most popular online News portals of Bangladesh updating 24/7 with breaking, political, business, entertainment, sports, lifestyle and crime news

LIVE PROJECTS

WEB APPLICATION, RESIDENTIAL INTERNET

Link: http://resnet.tilbd.net

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Dec 2020-Mar 2020

Trust Innovation Limited is playing a major role in the cantonment area by providing better services especially for internet service delivery.

WEB APPLICATION, SAFETY GPS TRACKER

Link: https://safetygpstracker.com.bd
Dhaka, Bangladesh — Jan 2020-Mar 2020

Safety GPS Tracker offer real time GPS Vehicle Tracking Solution. Our GPS Tracking Software enables you to track accurate location of your Fleet & Vehicles.

WEBSITE, BD24REPORT

Link: https://bd24report.com

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Jan 2020-Mar 2020

Bd24report was established on March 31, 2015. Within a very little time, it has managed to acquire a readers' base of around 35 million per month and is marked as one of the top multi news websites in Bangladesh currently.

WEB APPLICATION, P-PEEP FOOD EXPRESS

Link: http://ppeepbd.com

Dhaka, Bangladesh — nov 2020-Feb 2020

Bd Case Reference is the first free online case reference in Bangladesh which helps to find specific case references or decisions of the Supreme Court of Bangladesh.

WEB APPLICATION, BD CASE REFERENCE

Link: https://bdcasereference.com

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Sep 2019-nov 2019

Bd Case Reference is the first free online case reference in Bangladesh which helps to find specific case references or decisions of the Supreme Court of Bangladesh.

WEBSITE, DESHBAZAR

Link: https://deshbazar.com.bd

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Jan 2019–Sep 2019

Ghorey Boshe launches effective January 18, 2015 as an e-commerce portal in Bangladesh. Ghoreyboshe.com is an online marketplace where anyone can sell or buy almost everything



TRAINING COURSES

WEB DEVELOPMENT

leverage on Information and Communication Technologies (LICT) — NOV 2017-FEB 2018

Name: Frontend and Backend Development

Language: Php,javascript,mysql

Framework: Laravel

Batch: 19



WEB DESIGEN

Bangladesh Association of Software and Information Services (BASIS) — Jan 2017-Mar 2017

Name: Professional Web Design

Learning Item: Html,css,Bootstrap,Javascript

Batch: 61

GRAPHIC DESIGNE

MIST — Jan 2016-Mar 2016

Name: Professional Graphic Design

Software: Photoshop Cs6

Batch: 3

EDUCATION

B.SC. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

Daffodil International University — 2016-2020

Last 2 years CGPA: 3.78 Total CGPA:3.43

Passing Year: 2020



HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE (HSC)

Satkhira govt college — 2015-2016

Result: A Board: Jessore Passing year: 2015

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE (SSC)

Satkhira govt high school — 2013-2015

Result: A Board: Jessore Passing year: 2013



MEMBERSHIP

Programming club: Daffodil International University Computer & Programming Club Cultural Club: Daffodil International University Cultural Club

LANGUAGES



Bangla: native language

English: intermediate (speaking, reading); basic (writing)

INTEREST

First of all I love music, country music is my favorite. Love watching football, movies and playing games with my buddies. I spend quite a lot of time in traveling and photography, these keeps me fresh for working environment.



- Music
- Gaming
- Photography
- Cricket
- Traveling
- Movies

SIGNATURE

(MD.Khasrur Rahman) Date: 04-08-2021